Guide to the Eldon Dedini Papers
The Ohio State University Billy Ireland Cartoon Library & Museum
- Series IX. Research Files, 1950s-2000s, Undated
  - Bees, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 35)
  - Birds, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 36)
  - Beds, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 37)
  - Baseball, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 38)
  - Eastwood, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 39)
  - Boehm Quintette, Undated (Box ED 69, Folder 40)
  - Instant Type, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 5)
  - Facades, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 6)
  - New York City, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 7)
  - New York City Taxis, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 8)
  - Store Fronts, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 9)
  - NYC Restaurants, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 10)
  - NYC Buildings, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 11)
  - World Trade Center, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 12)
  - NYC Hotels, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 13)
  - Travel, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 14)
  - Washington, D.C. Supreme Court, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 15)
  - The White House, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 16)
  - Clinton Caricatures, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 17)
  - Sicilians, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 18)
  - Monterey- Carmel, People and Places, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 19)
  - Autos, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 20)
  - King City, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 21)
  - China and Chinese Art, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 22)
  - Old Ladies, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 23)
  - Facts and Fancies, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 24)
  - Banks- Debit and Credit Cards, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 25)
  - Business, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 26)
  - Contemporary Clothes, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 27)
  - Wall Street, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 28)
  - NYC Maps, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 29)
  - Latinos, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 30)
  - Robots, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 31)
  - Varga, Undated (Box ED 96, Folder 32)
  - Doonesbury, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 1)
  - Mythology, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 2)
  - Last Temptation of Christ Movie, 1988 (Box ED 98, Folder 3)
  - Hiroshima, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 4)
  - Sculpture and Statues, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 5)
  - Thanksgiving: Pilgrims, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 6)
  - Cats and Dogs, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 7)
  - Church: Religion, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 8)
  - Op-Ed Articles, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 9)
  - Funnies, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 10)
  - Ideas, Letters, Writings- Thoughts, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 11)
  - Photographs to be used as Backgrounds, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 12)
  - Fortune Cookie Slips, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 13)
  - Petty, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 28)
- Series X. Professional and Charitable Organizations, 1960s-2005, Undated
  This series contains materials related to any organizations that he was a part of, both professional and charitable. There's a good amount from the National Cartoonist Society and Cannery Row, which he played a role in helping restore.
  - Northern California Cartoon and Humor Association, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 1)
  - Art in America, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 2)
  - Masks, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 3)
  - Longtimers, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 4)
  - Wit, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 5)
  - Sam Seagull Awards, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 6)
  - Pica, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 7)
  - Pica, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 8)
  - Amici D'Italia, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 9)
  - Lyceum (Lecture info), Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 10)
  - Library of Congress, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 11)
  - NCS, 2005 (Box ED 70, Folder 12)
  - Exhibitions, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Humor, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 14)
  - Chouinard Foundation, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 15)
  - Museum Basel, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 16)
  - Contracts, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 17)
  - Cartoonist Profiles, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 18)
  - Charities, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 19)
  - Carmel Art Association, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 20)
  - Cartoon Art Museum, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 21)
  - Reprint Info, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 22)
  - Sales, CA By-laws, Financials, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 23)
  - Population Institute, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 24)
  - Schulz, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 25)
  - Membership folder Schulz Museum, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 26)
  - Cartoon Art Museum San Francisco, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 27)
  - Museum of Cartoon Art, Undated (Box ED 70, Folder 28)
  - NCS, 2003 (Box ED 71, Folder 1)
  - Northern Cal. NCS chapter, Undated (Box ED 71, Folder 2)
  - Simpsons cover of The Cartoonist, NCS Publication, 2003 (Box ED 71, Folder 3)
  - Munich Basel, Undated (Box ED 72, Folder 2)
  - Carmel Art Association, Undated (Box ED 71, Folder 4)
  - Cartoon Museum San Francisco, Undated (Box ED 71, Folder 5)
  - Dedini Biography, Undated (Box ED 72, Folder 1)
  - Cartoonist Guild, Paper on underground comics, Contract info, Undated (Box ED 71, Folder 6)
  - NCS 1, Undated (Box ED 71, Folder 7)
  - NCS 2, Undated (Box ED 71, Folder 8)
  - NCS 3, Undated (Box ED 71, Folder 9)
  - NCS 80s, 1980s (Box ED 71, Folder 10)
  - Cartoonist Association, Undated (Box ED 71, Folder 11)
  - NCS 1995-97, 1995-1997 (Box ED 71, Folder 12)
  - NCS 1988 Caniff Tributes, Nomination Sheets, Cartoonist publications, Rueben dinner (Box ED 73, Folder 1)
  - Magazine Cartoonists Guild, Undated (Box ED 73, Folder 2)
  - NCS 1, includes ED winning year 1963 (Box ED 73, Folder 3)
  - Cartoonists Guild, Undated (Box ED 73, Folder 4)
  - National Cartoonists Society, Undated (Box ED 73, Folder 5)
  - Inklings, Inks, and Cartoon Times publications, Undated (Box ED 73, Folder 6)
  - Pacific Grove Arts Center, Undated (Box ED 73, Folder 7)
  - Milito, Undated (Box ED 73, Folder 8)
  - Mozart, Undated (Box ED 73, Folder 9)
  - Carmel Art Association, Undated (Box ED 73, Folder 10)
  - Stacy, Los Olivos, Solvang, St. Mark's, Undated (Box ED 73, Folder 11)
  - Sanctuary, Asa Butterfield, Undated (Box ED 73, Folder 12)
  - Magazine Cartoonists Guild, Undated (Box ED 74, Folder 1)
  - NPAC (National Peace Action Coalition), Undated (Box ED 74, Folder 2)
  - Hatton Canyon, Undated (Box ED 74, Folder 3)
  - Hatton Canyon, 1997 (Box ED 74, Folder 4)
  - Film Festival, Undated (Box ED 74, Folder 5-9)
  - Images of the Pacific Biological Laboratory and Club by Harlan and Louise Watkins, The Eldon Dedini Collection, Undated (Box ED 74, Folder 10)
  - Dedini designed note cards to benefit Sabin-McEwen Learning Institute, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 14)
  - Committee for Hatton Canyon Scenic Highwat, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 15)
  - "Certificate of Thanksgiving to Eldon and Virgina Dedini for Service to All Saints Episcopal Church", 2000 (Box ED 98, Folder 16)
  - "Certificate of High Honors to Virginia Conroy and Eldon Dedini for Outstanding Art Service to Leland High School", 1981 (Box ED 98, Folder 17)
  - National Cartoonists Society Certificate of Membership, 2003 (Box ED 98, Folder 18)
  - Carmel Art Association, 1999 (Box ED 98, Folder 19)
  - Cartoon Exhibition- Arriola, Dedini, Ketcham, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 20)
  - Cartoon Art Museum Exhibit- Dedini, Arriola, 1993 (Box ED 98, Folder 21)
  - San Francisco Art Commission, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 22)
  - Tuttle-Faul, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 23)
  - Exhibitions- Dedini, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 24)
  - Golden State Theatre, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 25)
  - Monterey Blues Festival, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 26)
  - Gallery of Fine Comic Art, Undated (Box ED 98, Folder 27)
  - Arriola, Dedini, Schulz, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 1)
  - Monterey Jazz Festival, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 2)
  - All Saints Church, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 3)
  - Gwenn Graham Concous d' Elegance, 1970 (Box ED 99, Folder 4)
  - Santa Ynez Valley Carriage Classic, 1994 (Box ED 99, Folder 5)
  - Cannery Row Foundation, The Western Flyer, 1984 (Box ED 97, Folder 4)
- Series XI. Correspondence, 1940-2000
  This series contains all of Dedini's correspondence materials.
  - S. L. Chandler, Undated (Box ED 74, Folder 10)
  - Geo. Czar, 1996 (Box ED 74, Folder 11)
  - Arriola, Undated (Box ED 74, Folder 12)
  - Ketcham, Undated (Box ED 74, Folder 13-14)
  - Walter Avery, Undated (Box ED 74, Folder 15)
  - Al Kaelin, Undated (Box ED 74, Folder 16-17)
  - Lou Grant, Undated (Box ED 74, Folder 18)
  - Archie Comics, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 1)
  - Hayward, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 2)
  - Foye Walkup, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 3)
  - Bill Bush, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 4)
  - Dintenfass, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 5)
  - New Yorker Collection (Cartoon Bank-Financials), Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 6)
  - Gardener, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 7)
  - Lu Nowels, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 8)
  - Alan Levy, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 9)
  - Nan, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 10)
  - Plamandon, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 11)
  - Bruno, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 12-13)
  - Hayward King, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 14)
  - Al Wiseman and Bill Alger Correspondence, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 15)
  - Deborah Adams, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 16)
  - Mark Cohen, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 17)
  - Schulz, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 18-19)
  - Eisbach, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 20)
  - Escobar, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 21)
  - Wink Musselman, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 22)
  - Akmakjian, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 23)
  - John Province, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 24)
  - Nancy Dowd, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 25)
  - Don Normark, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 26)
  - Chuck Stacy, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 27)
  - Ken Kearney, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 27)
  - Mayumi Ito, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 29)
  - Laura Iverson, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 29)
  - Dennis Renault, Undated (Box ED 75, Folder 31-33)
  - Foreign Correspondence, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 1)
  - Alex Koltchak, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 2)
  - Lescher, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 3)
  - Renault- The Sacramento Bee, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 4)
  - Hispanic Mission, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 5)
  - Wine Fest, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 6)
  - Nancy Gonzalez, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 7)
  - Santa Roslia, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 8)
  - Renault, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 9)
  - Art Bouthillier, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 10)
  - Bob Abel, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 11)
  - All Saints, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 12)
  - Woody Woodruff, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 13)
  - Mark Cohen, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 14)
  - Alex Koltchak Correspondence, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 15)
  - Clippings/Obituaries, etc., Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 16)
  - Idiot Requests, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 17)
  - Cartoon Sales Woody Woodruff, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 18)
  - Hannah, Beth, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 19)
  - Lanini, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 20-21)
  - Letters, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 22-23)
  - Tognazzini, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 24)
  - Claudio, 1999 (Box ED 76, Folder 25)
  - Bacciarini, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 26)
  - Anne Hall/Photos of Eldon, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 27)
  - The New Yorker Cartoon Bank, 2005 (Box ED 76, Folder 28)
  - Harper Collins, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 29)
  - Suzaan Boettger, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 30)
  - New York trip, Undated (Box ED 76, Folder 31)
  - Box of Letters from Larry Gardner, Undated (Box ED 77, Folder 1)
  - Hans Lehman articles and manuscript, Undated (Box ED 77, Folder 2-3)
  - Guide Dogs, Undated (Box ED 77, Folder 4)
  - Mark Briggs, Undated (Box ED 77, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Kurt Anderson, Undated (Box ED 77, Folder 6)
  - Fan Mail Portfolio, Undated (Box ED 77, Folder 7)
  - Davis Langdale Gallery, "Artists of The New Yorker" show, 2000 (Box ED 77, Folder 8)
  - 1989 March of Dimes work (Box ED 77, Folder 9)
  - Christmas Cards, Undated (Box ED 77, Folder 10-12)
  - Saturday Review, Undated (Box ED 78, Folder 1)
  - Press and Letters, Undated (Box ED 78, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 78, Folder 3-4)
  - Fan Mail, Undated (Box ED 78, Folder 5)
  - Seti, Undated (Box ED 78, Folder 6)
  - Cartoon Letters, Undated (Box ED 78, Folder 7)
  - Fan Mail Sent/Answered, Undated (Box ED 78, Folder 8)
  - Fan mail, Undated (Box ED 78, Folder 9-13)
  - Lucy Caswell, Ohio State Donations, Undated (Box ED 78, Folder 14)
  - Ohio State Correspondence, Undated (Box ED 78, Folder 15-20)
  - Tor Odemark, Undated (Box ED 78, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1969, 1970, 1983-1985 (Box ED 78, Folder 22-23)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box ED 79, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Early, 1940s (Box ED 79, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1950s (Box ED 79, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box ED 79, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box ED 79, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box ED 79, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box ED 79, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1964 (Box ED 79, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box ED 79, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box ED 79, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box ED 79, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box ED 79, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box ED 79, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box ED 79, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box ED 79, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1989, 1990, 1994 (Box ED 79, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box ED 79, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box ED 79, Folder 18)
  - Unfiled, Letter to Jerry Beatty regarding Kennedy Assassination, Undated (Box ED 79, Folder 19)
  - Poka, Undated (Box ED 79, Folder 20)
  - Larry Gardner, 2003 (Box ED 99, Folder 6)
  - Postcard from Joanne and Hank Ketcham, 1959 (Box ED 99, Folder 7)
  - Assorted Correspondence, 2000s (Box ED 99, Folder 8)
  - Sylvan Candasa, 1990s (Box ED 99, Folder 9)
  - Addison-Wesley Publishing, 1986 (Box ED 99, Folder 10)
  - Reuben Pearson, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Alumni Association- Posters, 1966 (Box ED 99, Folder 12)
  - Georg Czar (2 Folders), Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 13-14)
  - Barbara Shermund Letters and Gag Records, 1950s (Box ED 99, Folder 15)
  - Barbara Shermund Correspondence, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 16)
  - Barbara Shermund for Lisa Donnelly, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 17)
  - Barbara Shermund, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 18)
  - Bob Harvey, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 19)
  - Matteson, 1983-2000 (Box ED 99, Folder 20)
  - Leon Barwood, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 21)
  - Anson Musselman, 2005 (Box ED 99, Folder 22)
  - Fantagraphics, 2005 (Box ED 99, Folder 23)
  - Inter-Global Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Cartoonists, 1966 (Box ED 99, Folder 24)
  - John and Roberta Province, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 25)
  - Fan Mail, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 26)
  - Christmas Cards, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 27)
  - Autograph Requests, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 28)
  - Foreign Fan Mail, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 29)
  - Fan Mail, Undated (Box ED 99, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box ED 100, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box ED 100, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box ED 100, Folder 3)
- Series XII. Personal and Family Materials, 1921-2006, Undated
  This series contains any personal or family material. Although many materials in this series are undated, it is presumed to have been created or collected during Dedini's lifetime.
  - St. Francis Retreat- Cursillo, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 1)
  - Monterey Graphics, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 2)
  - Medical Bills and Records, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 3-5)
  - Geo. Czars, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 6)
  - Hungarian Revolution, 1956 (Box ED 80, Folder 7)
  - Hella, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 8)
  - Clippings about Dedini, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 9)
  - Datebook, 1986 (Box ED 81, Folder 1)
  - Postcards from out first trip to Franc, Italy, and Switzerland, 1955 (Box ED 80, Folder 10)
  - New Yorker Desk Diaries, 1979-1992 (Box ED 81, Folder 2-14)
  - Ancestors, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 12)
  - Hungary, Vienna, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 13)
  - Photos, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 14-16)
  - 2 Handmade cat masks labeled Eldon and Virginia, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 17)
  - Church Directories and Christmas Programs, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 18)
  - New Yorker Desk Diaries, 1993-2006 (Box ED 82, Folder 1-12)
  - 50th Wedding Anniversary, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Conroy exhibitions pamphlets, Undated (Box ED 80, Folder 19)
  - Scoop article, 1975 (Box ED 83, Folder 1)
  - Conversations with Members of the Pacific Biological Cannery Row Oral History Project, 1999 (Box ED 83, Folder 2)
  - Old Letters, Undated (Box ED 83, Folder 3)
  - Romie, Undated (Box ED 83, Folder 4)
  - Guilio's Folder from Grade 3, Undated (Box ED 83, Folder 5)
  - Dedini Stationary, Undated (Box ED 83, Folder 6)
  - Birthday Cards created by Eldon, Undated (Box ED 83, Folder 7)
  - V. Conroy Exhibit, Undated (Box ED 83, Folder 8)
  - V. Conroy, Undated (Box ED 83, Folder 9-10)
  - Printed Bios, Undated (Box ED 83, Folder 11)
  - Virginia and Eldon 50th Anniversary Guest Book, Undated (Box ED 83, Folder 12)
  - 50th Anniversary, Undated (Box ED 83, Folder 13)
  - Renault, Undated (Box ED 83, Folder 14)
  - 2 Account Books, 1975-1991, 1991-1999 (Box ED 84, Folder 1-2)
  - Programs from Eldon Dedini's Memorial Service, Undated (Box ED 84, Folder 3)
  - Romilda Dedini notebooks, Undated (Box ED 84, Folder 4)
  - Photograph of Eldon, Undated (Box ED 84, Folder 5)
  - School Children Work and Fire Prevention Day, Undated (Box ED 84, Folder 6)
  - Wedding, Undated (Box ED 84, Folder 7)
  - King City Jolon, Undated (Box ED 72, Folder 3)
  - All Saints Patter History-Newsletters, Undated (Box ED 84, Folder 8)
  - Wine, Undated (Box ED 84, Folder 9)
  - Wine, Undated (Box ED 84, Folder 10-11)
  - Wine Labels, Undated (Box ED 84, Folder 12)
  - 5 Notebooks- recipes, travel, notes, addresses, 1960, 1963, 1978, 1981, Undated (Box ED 84, Folder 13-17)
  - 2 Account books, 1999-2002, 2002-2005 (Box ED 84, Folder 18-19)
  - The Monterey County Herald, posthumous article about Dedini, Saturday, January 16, 2006 (Box ED 85, Folder 1)
  - School Diploma, Awards, etc., Undated (Box ED 85, Folder 2)
  - King City Union High School Memories book, 1939 (Box ED 85, Folder 3)
  - Anthologies, Dedini Cartoon History and Dates, Undated (Box ED 100, Folder 4)
  - Copy of Eldon Dedini's Birth Certificate, 1921 (Box ED 100, Folder 5)
  - Cards from Grandmother, 1920s-1930s (Box ED 100, Folder 6)
  - Eldon Dedini Childhood Drawings, 1920s (Box ED 100, Folder 7)
  - Composition Book, 1929 (Box ED 100, Folder 8)
  - Photocopy of King City Union Grammar School Commencement Program, 1935 (Box ED 100, Folder 9)
  - Algebra I Homework, 1937 (Box ED 100, Folder 10)
  - Admission Inquiries to Art Schools, 1938 (Box ED 100, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Raye Burns re: paper recommendations, 1938 (Box ED 100, Folder 12)
  - King City Union High School Commencement Announcement, 1939 (Box ED 100, Folder 13)
  - Christmas and Birthday Cards, 1940s (Box ED 100, Folder 14)
  - Friends in Faith (2 Folders), 2000s (Box ED 100, Folder 15-16)
  - Wedding Portrait of Eldon Dedini's Parents, Grutly Steve Dedini and Oleta Regina Loeber, 1920 (Box ED 100, Folder 17)
  - "Mission Ranch Saturday Nite" Photograph, Undated (Box ED 100, Folder 18)
  - Pictures for Teresa, Photograph of Eldon Dedini in front of "Stop Durate" drawing, ca. 2000s (Box ED 100, Folder 19)
  - Photographs of Dedini Family, Friends, Events, 1980s-1990s (Box ED 100, Folder 20)
  - Binder of French Language Lessons, 1980 (Box ED 100, Folder 21)
  - Binder of Italian Language Lessons, Undated (Box ED 100, Folder 22)
- Series XIII. Memorabilia, 1920s-2000s, Undated
  This series contains memorabilia associated with Dedini. This includes tools he used to create his cartoons, inspiration material from his childhood, and even a gilded baby shoe that his mother kept with his name on the bottom.
  - Cannery Row, Undated (Box ED 85, Folder 4-6)
  - Assorted Clippings, Undated (Box ED 85, Folder 7)
  - Great Cannery Row Reunion, Undated (Box ED 85, Folder 8)
  - Comic Stamps, Undated (Box ED 85, Folder 9)
  - Dedini Designed T-Shirts, Undated (Box ED 86, Folder 1)
  - PG Art Center Dedini Night, Undated (Box ED 85, Folder 10)
  - Old Del Monte (cap with Dedini art), Undated (Box ED 85, Folder 11)
  - Playboy Club Keycards, 1977-1985 (Box ED 87, Folder 1-10)
  - NCS Cartooning Awards, 1958, 1964 (Box ED 87, Folder 11-12)
  - Playboy awards/plaques, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 13-14)
  - Notes for Dedini album, sketchbook, 1959-1963 (Box ED 87, Folder 15)
  - To be mounted in notebook, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 16)
  - Cigar box with crayons, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 17)
  - Gilded Baby Shoe with Eldon written on the bottom, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 18)
  - Picasso Scarf, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 19)
  - White Pencil, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 20)
  - Absolut Vodka Handkerchief, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 21)
  - Grove-Portola Savings Matchbox, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 22-23)
  - Celebrate Snoopy Invitation, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 24)
  - Ritmo Charcoal Pencils, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 25)
  - Koh-i-norr box of pencils, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 26)
  - Assorted "Peanuts" pins, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 27-32)
  - Big John's Sangria Bottle (label by Dedini), Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 33)
  - California Wine Guild (label by Dedini), Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 34)
  - Concours d'Elegance Pin, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 35)
  - Tour de Farce pin, Undated (Box ED 87, Folder 36)
  - Disney/ Universal, Undated (Box ED 88, Folder 1)
  - Disney, Background and Character Sketches, 1944-1946 (Box ED 88, Folder 2)
    No artist's signature; believed to be work of Dedini and other Disney Artists
  - Continuity Sketches; Camera Angle; Universal Sketchbook, 1944-1946 (Box ED 88, Folder 3)
  - Disney Character Sketches; includes Seven Dwarfs and Pinocchio, ca.1944-1946 (Box ED 88, Folder 4)
  - Disney Photostats and Model Sheets, ca.1944-1946 (Box ED 88, Folder 5)
    Dedini may not be the artists of the characters depicted in the photostats and modelsheets
  - Pay stubs from Walt Disney Productions and Universal Pictures, 1944-1946 (Box ED 88, Folder 6)
  - Disney Model sheets, ca.1944-1946 (Box ED 88, Folder 7)
  - Disney Photostats, model sheets (some mine- some Johnny Cannon and others), ca.1944-1946 (Box ED 88, Folder 8)
    Note written on folder by Eldon Dedini: "Virginia and her family knew Johnny Cannon (Disney animator). When Virginia's mother died I cleaned out her garage and found packages of model sheets, story sketches, misc.etc. Much water damaged- others good shape."
  - Screen Cartoonists Guild, 1945-1949 (Box ED 88, Folder 9)
  - Mickey and the Beanstalk; Fun & Fancy Free model sheets, ca.1944-1946 (Box ED 88, Folder 10)
  - Cards for Virginia from Eldon and Giulio, 1996-2002 (Box ED 88, Folder 11)
  - Pacific Grove at Center, V. Conroy Retrospective, 1995 (Box ED 88, Folder 12)
  - Costa Rica Trip, Undated (Box ED 88, Folder 13)
  - Clark Foundation Gus Arriola Event, 1996 (Box ED 88, Folder 14)
  - Laura L. McGregor Memorial Service, 1987 (Box ED 88, Folder 15)
  - New York Trip, 1990 (Box ED 88, Folder 16)
  - Postcards from Europe, Undated (Box ED 88, Folder 17)
  - Chouinard Art Institute of California Booklet, 1940s (Box ED 88, Folder 18)
  - Carmel-by-the-Sea 70th Anniversary, 1986 (Box ED 88, Folder 19)
  - Strong Vocational Interest Profile, 1968 (Box ED 88, Folder 20)
  - Biographies from The Carmel Pine Cone News, 1980s (Box ED 88, Folder 21)
  - Written Biographies, Undated (Box ED 88, Folder 22)
  - Sister Domenica, 1980s (Box ED 88, Folder 23)
  - Harlan Watkins; Personal Materials, 1940s-1950s (Box ED 88, Folder 24)
  - Certificate for Second Prize of the Population Cartoon Contest by The Population Institute, 1974 (Box ED 89, Folder 1)
  - Cloth Child's Book, 1920s (Box ED 89, Folder 2)
  - Gasoline Alley Caricatures, 1920s (Box ED 89, Folder 3)
  - I [heart] Race Walking cap (logo by Dedini), Undated (Box ED 89, Folder 4)